# SIWON JANG

# **Embedded System Software Engineer**

Email sion.jang@gmail.com

Mobile +82 10 6239 2602

Portfolio https://sion-jang.github.io/portfolio/index.html





#### **Profile**

With over 12 years of experience in software developing and providing technical support in set-top box industry & 3 years in software development of automotive industry.

Strong academic backgrounds in Bachelor's Degree in control & instrumentation engineering which includes embedded system software architecture, peripheral device driver

implementation/validation, bootloader implementation/validation and networking.



## **Employment History**

Jan 2019 – Present Mando-Hella Electronics

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

- SW Technical Manager
- · Rear Occupant Alert Radar
- Driver Monitoring System

Mar 2018 – Jan 2019 HUMAX / Automotive

#### **Senior Software Engineer**

- SW Technical Manager on Automotive Smart Antenna project
- Device Drivers of Automotive Linux Platform

Dec 2011 – Feb 2018 HUMAX / STB

## **Senior Software Engineer**

- Device Drivers of STB(Set-top Box) Linux platform
- Coaching embedded SW for VietNam R&D

Dec 2005 – Nov 2011

**DMT** 

Skills

#### **Junior Software Engineer**

• Junior SW Engineer of STB Device Driver and Application



## **Skills and Languages**

- Embedded Linux SW / RTOS
- C / Shell Script program languages
- MATLAB
- · PHP, HTML
- MS Office
- Equipment Handling (Oscilloscopes, SFQ, Spectrum Analyzer, ...)

Languages

• Korean – Native / English - Intermediate



### Education

• Bachelor of Dept. Control & Instrumentation Engineering, Myong-Ji University, Korea



## References

Available on request